

# ANDRÉS FELIPE CEBALLOS MARTINEZ

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

NAME: ANDRÉS FELIPE CEBALLOS MARTINEZ IDENTITY

**DOCUMENT:** CC.1116256884

DATE OF BIRTH: December 1st, 1992

ADDRESS: kra 9a # 119 - 70 Bogota, Colombia

MOBILE: +57 315 210 3480

**E-MAIL:** ceballosmarandres@gmail.com

LINKEDIN PROFILE: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andresceballosm/

#### **PROFILE**

FullStack developer with more than 7 years of experience in projects for banks, retail, sports, and telecommunications companies, development in Javascript with the use of frameworks and libraries like NodeJS(with Typescript), React Native(redux, hooks, redux-sagas, AR/VR, Typescript), Ionic and Nativescript for mobile development and ReactJS, NextJS, Angular and Jquery for web development, also use of databases relational and No relational like Mysql, Postgresql, MongoDB, CouchDB, and firebase. On the other hand, I've used platforms like AWS, Heroku, Google cloud, and Vercel among other technologies for the Cloud. Also, I've used tools for code administration like Jira, Git, Sonar, Gulp, Webpack, Appcenter, Sentry, and docker. knowledge in web3 with Ethereum, Solidity, Hardhat, Truffle, Metamask,ethersjs, and web3js.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### 05/2023 - Present

#### Truenorth

- Developing features on React Native for Fintech App
- Pull Requests review

# **Sr Software Developer**

01/2023 - 05/2023

#### **CloudDevs**

- Developing features on React Native for iOS application(Typescript, sqlite, Sentry, unit test etc)
- Collaborating with the dev team to identify and fix technical problems.
- Pull Requests review

# **Technical Lead Engineer**

09/2021 - 01/2023

#### **Devbase**

- Designing the application architecture.
- Developing features on React Native(Typescript, Apollo GraphQL, Appcenter, Sentry, unit test etc) and NodeJS(AWS, Typescript, Apollo Server, unit test, ).
- Delegating work and assignments to the dev team.
- Developing landing page on NextJS
- Collaborating with the dev team to identify and fix technical problems.
- Pull Requests review

### Sr Web UI Developer

11/2020 - 09/2021

# Globant

- Developing Loans and Cards(Micro frontends) Platform to Santander Bank on ReactJS with Unit test on Jest, styled-components, redux, and Git.
- Pull Requests review

**FullStack Developer** 

02/2018 - 11/2020

**Nexos Software (remote)** 

- Developing a Platform to repair devices on React Native with typescript,Redux(Unit Test), and web platform builder on ReactJS with typescript and redux. App for donations developing API Rest on NodeJS, app mobile on React Native (Redux, redux-sagas, redux-form, Unit Test).
- Developing App for Retail, developing Backend on NodeJS, app mobile React Native(Redux, Redux-Sagas, Redux-Form, Unit Test).
- Developing and maintenance of the Bancolombia(Bank) App.
- Developing new features Davivienda App(Bank) for Salvador, Honduras, Panama, Costa Rica, and Colombia.
- Developing App in Nativescript for travel agency Checking the code quality with Sonar. • Deployments with Jenkis. • TDD • AR/VR.

# Mobile Developer 11/2017 – 02/2018 Itehl Consulting

 Developing app with a focus in the commercial area of AVANTEL company, using Phonegap(Android and IOS) with API communication to Backend in Java and database in oracle.

# FullStack developer 09/2015 – 10/2017 Freelance

 Developing mobile apps with framework Ionic 2, HTML5 technology, AngularJS Angular 2, databases relational and NoRelational, MySQL, Jquery, CSS, and Services on NodeJS.

#### **EDUCATION**

Agroindustrial Engineering, Gran Colombia University Armenia, Colombia 2015

# **OTHER COURSES**

- Learn to program with Go(Golang), duration 25,5 hours.
- Development full-stack practice: Professional configuration of projects, duration 3 hours 49 min, Course completed on Sep 2018.
- Docker esencial, duration 2 hours 19 min, course completed on Sep 2018. Gulp.js, Git, and Browserify: Web Project Workflows, Course completed on Sep 2018, duration 2 hours 40 min.

- Learning Redux, Course completed on Sep 2018, duration 2 hours 59 min. React.js Essential Training, Course completed on Sep 2018, duration 3 hours 15 min.
- Course from zero to expert creating applications (Angular 6+), duration 25 hours.
- Course React-native+redux+redux-saga+firebase, duration 19,5 hours. SAP ABAP programming, by Logali group, education school SAP, In progress 180 hours.
- SAP concepto e iniciación, by Logali group, education school SAP, duration 5 hours, Finish Bogotá, January 2018.
- High school, Comfamiliar school, Valle del Cauca Colombia, 2010.

Link certifications

https://drive.google.com/open?id=1x8C8G7VVUK5hG4bz0sCw8A9q7uzIW8-W

## **REFERENCES**

Name: Juan Sebastián Martínez Marín

Occupation: Systems engineer Company: Seguros Bolivar

Phone: 3114209791

Name: Ginna Paola Vargas

Occupation: Professional international business

Company: Independent

Phone: 3156317623